<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" name="JSFXClones" commit="f2440722590127a7e69c8bce318c3c56d1e0ffa1">
  <category name="jsfx">
    <reapack name="JClones_AC1.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_AC1">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_AC1\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_AC1 is a clone of a plugin, designed to emulate the characteristics and sonic qualities of analog mixing consoles. By simulating the behavior of analog circuits, the plugin brings the warmth, depth, and harmonic richness of analog gear to digital audio productions. The plugin is highly regarded for its ability to add subtle compression, harmonic distortion, and a sense of cohesion to mixes, making them sound more polished and professional.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Parameters\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Input Gain:} Adjusts the input signal level before processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Output Gain:} Sets the final output level after processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Auto Gain:} Engages primitive loudness compensation algorithm.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Drive:} Controls the input signal level for saturation and harmonic distortion.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Comp (Compression):} Adjusts the amount of soft-knee compression applied.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Attack:} Controls the compressor's response to transients.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Release:} Determines the compressor's recovery speed after compression.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Also the clone version adds extra parameters:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Stereo Link:} allows to run the processing in linked stereo or dual-mono mode.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Mode:} allows to switch the compression curve to more recent version of the cloned plugin (the newer curve offers more aggressive and less analog behaviour).\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_AC1.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-06-28T15:20:22Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/eaed11c2c419950a62760395de17f30921f71f5d/jsfx/JClones_AC1.jsfx</source>
        <source file="JClones_AC1.jsfx.rpl">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/eaed11c2c419950a62760395de17f30921f71f5d/jsfx/JClones_AC1.jsfx.rpl</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_AC2.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_AC2">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_AC2\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_AC2 is a clone of a plugin designed to emulate the classic sound and behavior of analog tape machines that captures the essence of tape saturation, compression, and harmonic richness, making it an invaluable asset for adding depth, warmth, and character to digital recordings. The plugin provides a range of controls that allow users to fine-tune the tape emulation to suit various audio materials and production styles.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Parameters\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Input Gain:} Adjusts the input signal level before processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Output Gain:} Sets the final output level after processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Auto Gain:} Engages primitive loudness compensation algorithm.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Rolloff:} Controls the attenuation of high frequencies, simulating the natural frequency response of analog tape, which tends to soften or "roll off" the high-end as part of its characteristic sound.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Bump:} Adds a distinctive low-end enhancement or "bump," reminiscent of the subtle bass lift that can occur when audio is recorded to or played back from analog tape.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Model:} Sets playback head type model:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Swiss:} Modeled after Swiss-made tape machines known for their precision and high-fidelity sound (Studer A80 mkII).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Japan-O:} Represents a tape machine from Japan, known for its balanced tonal qualities and slightly warm character (Otari MX-80).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b USA-M:} Modeled after a classic American tape machine, famous for its robust and punchy sound (MCI JH-24).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b USA-A:} Based on another renowned American tape machine, known for its aggressive saturation and strong coloration (Ampex MM-1200).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Japan-S:} Represents a Japanese tape machine with a smooth, silky sound, often used in high-quality studio recordings (Sony APR-5000).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Japan-T:} Modeled after a Japanese tape machine noted for its tight, punchy low end and clear, defined high frequencies (Tascam ATR-60).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Bias:} controls the tape bias setting, which refers to a high-frequency signal added to the audio signal before recording onto tape. Adjusting the bias affects the tonal balance, saturation, and overall character of the tape emulation.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Release:} Controls the time it takes for the dynamic processing to return to its normal state after the input signal level decreases. This is crucial in the context of tape emulation because it simulates the behavior of the tape as it responds to changes in the audio signal, affecting how the saturation and compression characteristics are applied over time.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Speed:} Tape speed: 7.5, 15 or 30 inch per second (IPS).\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b EQ Type:} Allows users to choose between different equalization curves that emulate the frequency response characteristics of classic tape machines. The IEC-1 and IEC-2 options represent different International Electrotechnical Commission (IEC) standards for tape equalization. These settings affect the overall tonal balance of the tape emulation by applying specific equalization curves commonly associated with different tape recording and playback standards.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b IEC-1:} Use this setting to add warmth and fullness to tracks, particularly those needing a boost in the low-end or a smooth high-end roll-off. It's perfect for creating a vintage tape sound with a rich bass response.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b IEC-2:} Opt for this setting when you want to maintain clarity and detail in the mid and high frequencies. It's ideal for modern productions where a crisp, bright tape effect is desired without too much low-end emphasis.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Tape:} Sets tape formulation:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Modern:} current manufacturing technologies create a tape with a much greater dynamic range than earlier formulations. These tapes have a large linear region, and hence have a smaller non-linear (saturation) 'character'. This makes for recordings as true as possible to the original material.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Vintage:} older tape mediums tend to have less dynamic range, and suffer from greater distortion/saturation. These tapes, however, have 'character' that newer ones do not, and have been used with great success in recording audio.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_AC2.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-06-30T13:16:04Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/8a1d5b307326ea0f15ea59b86dbcf3deb47daab7/jsfx/JClones_AC2.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter is a clone of freeware limiter plugin designed to provide transparent limiting, allowing you to maximize the loudness of your audio tracks without introducing distortion or unwanted artifacts. Simple interface, low CPU usage, and essential controls make it an excellent choice for both beginners and experienced producers looking to increase the loudness of their tracks. However, the developer of the plugin disappeared from the market abruptly around 2007.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Parameters\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Threshold:} Sets the level at which the limiting begins. Any signal that exceeds this threshold will be limited. Lower the threshold to apply more limiting and increase the perceived loudness of the audio.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-07-18T18:15:30Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/bd6d27854c3f0f3d170d19283d8061f9244b247d/jsfx/JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_L2.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_L2">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_L2\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_L2 is a clone of a highly regarded audio plugin known for its capabilities in mastering and dynamic range control. Featuring a state-of-the-art brickwall limiter with look-ahead technology, it ensures peak control and prevents clipping. Its intelligent release control adapts to the audio signal, providing smooth and transparent limiting without manual adjustments. The plugin also includes advanced dithering and noise shaping options to preserve audio quality when reducing bit depth.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Controls\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Threshold:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Sets the level at which the limiting begins.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Typically ranges from 0 dB down to -30 dB.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Lowering the threshold increases the amount of gain reduction applied, making the audio louder but reducing its dynamic range. Start with a moderate setting and adjust according to the desired loudness and dynamic control.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Ceiling (Output Ceiling):\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Determines the maximum output level after processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Can be set from 0 dB down to -30 dB.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Setting the output ceiling slightly below 0 dB (commonly around -0.1 dB to -0.3 dB) prevents clipping and allows headroom for digital playback systems. Adjust based on your final output format requirements.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Release:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Controls the speed at which the limiter stops reducing gain after the input signal drops below the threshold.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Ranges from 0.01 ms to 1,000 ms.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Short release times (fast) are suitable for transient-rich material like drums but can introduce distortion if too short. Longer release times (slow) provide a smoother sound but can cause pumping. It\u8217's often effective to use the "Auto Release" (Auto Release Control) mode, which dynamically adjusts the release time to suit the incoming audio.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Advanced Controls\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Quantize:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Sets the target bit depth for the processed audio.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Options:} Choices include 24-bit, 22-bit, 20-bit, 18-bit, and 16-bit.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Choose the bit depth based on the final delivery format. For instance, 16-bit is standard for CD audio. If no bit depth reduction is required, set it to 24-bit.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Dither:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Adds low-level noise to mask quantization distortion when reducing bit depth.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Options:} Type 1 and Type 2.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Type 1:} Suitable for most material; provides a good balance between noise and distortion masking.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Type 2:} Used for recordings with very low-level detail and high dynamic range; it has a slightly different noise character.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Choose the dither type based on the material and the desired noise profile. Typically, Type 1 is a safe choice for most applications.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Shaping:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Adjusts the frequency spectrum of the dithering noise to make it less audible.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Options:} None, Moderate, Normal, and Ultra.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b None:} Applies no noise shaping.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Moderate:} Minimal shaping, less aggressive than other options.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Normal:} Standard shaping that is effective in most cases.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Ultra:} Aggressive shaping for critical listening and mastering.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Choose the level of noise shaping based on the final output medium and the need to minimize audible noise. \u8220"Normal\u8221" is generally effective, but for critical mastering, \u8220"Ultra\u8221" might be preferable.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_L2.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-06-22T17:26:21Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/7560c0a8b6831662cbab27c34b1436eca1d8529e/jsfx/JClones_L2.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_OInflator.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_OInflator">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_OInflator\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_OInflator is a clone of a plugin renowned for its ability to enhance perceived loudness, warmth, and presence in audio without introducing distortion or reducing dynamic range. It operates by applying a unique process of harmonic enhancement that boosts the audio signal's energy, making it sound fuller and more impactful. Ideal for adding depth and richness to any audio source, it remains a go-to tool for professionals seeking to elevate their mixes with controlled and transparent processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Controls\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Input:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Adjusts the level of the signal entering the Inflator.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Use this control to ensure the input signal is at an optimal level before processing. This helps in achieving the desired loudness and character without clipping or unwanted distortion. Start with the input at a neutral level and adjust as needed to match the output and desired effect.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Effect:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Determines the amount of the Inflator's effect applied to the audio signal.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} 0% to 100%.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Increasing the Effect level enhances the perceived loudness, warmth, and punch of the audio. At lower levels, the effect is subtle, while higher levels introduce a more pronounced, fuller sound. Start at a lower percentage and gradually increase until you achieve the desired enhancement.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Curve:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Shapes the characteristic of the enhancement effect applied by the Inflator.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} -50% to +50%.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Negative Curve Values (-50% to 0%):} Provide a softer, more rounded enhancement, ideal for preserving the natural dynamics and warmth of the audio.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Positive Curve Values (0% to +50%):} Offer a sharper, more aggressive enhancement, adding more punch and presence, which can be especially effective for drums or vocals.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Adjust this control to fine-tune the tonal character of the enhancement based on the specific needs of your audio material.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Output:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Sets the level of the signal after processing by the Inflator.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Use this control to balance the processed signal\u8217's level with other elements in your mix. It ensures that the overall volume remains consistent and prevents clipping. Start with the output at a neutral level and adjust as needed to match your mix.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Band Split Mode:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Band Split Mode allows for independent processing of three frequency bands (Low, Mid, and High), providing a more detailed and nuanced approach to enhancing different parts of the audio spectrum.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_OInflator.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-06-22T19:30:19Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/15f3f9d34194214a1bddce26feb7a0eee8c5bd5e/jsfx/JClones_OInflator.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_Phoenix.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_Phoenix">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_Phoenix\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_Phoenix is a clone of a renowned audio plugin designed to emulate the sound characteristics of analog tape recording. Created by a company known for its high-quality analog and digital audio equipment, the plugin is widely used by audio engineers and producers to add warmth, depth, and subtle harmonic distortion to digital recordings.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Parameters\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Input Trim\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Adjusts the level of the input signal before it is processed by the tape emulation.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Typically \u177?10 dB.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Increase the input trim to drive the signal harder into the tape effect, resulting in more pronounced saturation and harmonic distortion. Lower the trim for a cleaner, subtler effect. Use this control to set the initial level of processing intensity.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Process\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Controls the amount of tape saturation and harmonic distortion applied to the signal.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Variable from light to heavy saturation.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Increase the drive to add more analog warmth, compression, and harmonic richness. Higher drive settings emulate the effect of pushing tape harder, which is useful for adding depth and character to instruments and vocals. Adjust to taste depending on the desired level of tape coloration.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Output Trim\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Sets the final output level after the tape emulation process.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Range:} Typically \u177?6 dB.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Use the output trim to balance the level of the processed signal with the rest of your mix. This ensures that the enhanced audio fits seamlessly within the overall mix without causing level inconsistencies or clipping. Adjust to achieve the desired output volume.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Brightness\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Affects the way high frequencies are treated during the tape emulation process. It modifies the spectral balance by either enhancing or attenuating the upper frequencies, which can significantly influence the perceived clarity, presence, and airiness of the audio.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Options:}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Opal:} Designed to offer a neutral to slightly bright high-frequency response.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Gold:} Provides a balanced enhancement that brings out a smooth and warm high-frequency presence.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Sapphire:} Emphasizes high-frequency clarity and brightness, offering the most pronounced enhancement of the three modes.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Type (Tape Modes):\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Function:} Selects the specific tape emulation mode.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Options:}\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Luminescent:} Adds brightness and clarity with subtle tape coloration.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Iridescent:} Offers a balanced, all-purpose tape sound with moderate warmth.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Radiant:} Enhances midrange presence, adding richness and body.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Dark Essence:} Provides a darker, more saturated tone, emphasizing low-end warmth.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Luster:} Combines tape saturation with compression, producing a smooth and cohesive sound.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Usage:} Choose the mode that best suits the desired effect for the audio material. Experiment with different modes to find the perfect tonal character for your mix.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs28 Auto Gain:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 This function is added to JClones version to compensate gain boost in different tape modes.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_Phoenix.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-06-25T23:02:09Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/6c2548aa315023d94f82b15bf9d545e7ec929d18/jsfx/JClones_Phoenix.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
    <reapack name="JClones_RS124.jsfx" type="effect" desc="JClones_RS124">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 JClones_RS124\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_RS124 is a clone of the first emulation of classic vari-mu compressor, originally developed in the 1960s by technical engineers of famous recording studio. This plugin captures the unique sonic characteristics and behavior of the original hardware, which was famously used on numerous iconic recordings by The Beatles and other legendary artists.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Main Parameters\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Model:} The plugin offers three different models of the RS124 compressor, each with unique characteristics and sonic qualities. These models are based on different historical units used at Abbey Road Studios, and they capture the distinct behavior and tonal nuances of the original hardware units.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b 60050A}: Known for its smooth and musical compression.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b 61010B}: Features a faster attack and release time than the 60050A model.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b 60070B}: Strikes a balance between the 60050A and 61010B models in terms of attack and release times.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Input (Gain):} Adjusts the input level, determining how much signal is sent into the compressor.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Release (Time):} Allows users to choose between different release times, affecting how quickly the compressor returns to its normal state after reducing gain. Original version had stepped release control with dedicated "hold" position. JClones version offers smooth release control with "hold" mode removed for better usability.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b SuperFuse:} Engages a more aggressive compression curve, useful for adding more character and intensity to the compression effect. Original hardware unit didn't have such mode.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Output (Gain):} Controls the output level, ensuring the signal leaving the compressor is at the desired level. Original version had stepped output gain control. JClones version offers smooth output gain control for better usability.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\b Box Tone:} JClones version specific. Turns off audio coloration effect.\par}
}
]]></description>
        <link rel="website">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones</link>
        <link rel="screenshot">https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/assets/screenshots/JClones_RS124.png</link>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0.0" author="JClones" time="2024-07-17T18:12:16Z">
        <source>https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/2943d11793da7f7a0a17eaf5bc19f9804aea7841/jsfx/JClones_RS124.jsfx</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
  <metadata>
    <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0{\fonttbl{\f0 \fswiss Helvetica;}{\f1 Courier;}}
{\colortbl;\red255\green0\blue0;\red0\green0\blue255;}
\widowctrl\hyphauto

{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones\u8221" JSFX Plugins\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 Free {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://www.reaper.fm/sdk/js/"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
JSFX
}}}
 clones of popular audio plugins (without UI (yet)) to use in {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://www.reaper.fm/"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Reaper
}}}
.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs32 Installation\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 If you have the {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://reapack.com/"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
ReaPack Extension
}}}
 installed, you can add the repository to Reaper with this URL:\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \f1 https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/raw/master/index.xml\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 If you {\b don't} have ReaPack installed, you can also add these plugins on a per-file basis. Also you may use {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/jpcima/ysfx"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
ysfx
}}}
 or {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://www.reaper.fm/reaplugs/"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
ReaJS
}}}
 to run JSFX plugin in another DAW.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_L2\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_L2 is a clone of a highly regarded audio plugin known for its capabilities in mastering and dynamic range control. Featuring a state-of-the-art brickwall limiter with look-ahead technology, it ensures peak control and prevents clipping. Its intelligent release control adapts to the audio signal, providing smooth and transparent limiting without manual adjustments. The plugin also includes advanced dithering and noise shaping options to preserve audio quality when reducing bit depth.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_L2.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_OInflator\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_OInflator is a clone of a plugin renowned for its ability to enhance perceived loudness, warmth, and presence in audio without introducing distortion or reducing dynamic range. It operates by applying a unique process of harmonic enhancement that boosts the audio signal's energy, making it sound fuller and more impactful. Ideal for adding depth and richness to any audio source, it remains a go-to tool for professionals seeking to elevate their mixes with controlled and transparent processing.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_OInflator.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_Phoenix\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_Phoenix is a clone of a renowned audio plugin designed to emulate the sound characteristics of analog tape recording. Created by a company known for its high-quality analog and digital audio equipment, the plugin is widely used by audio engineers and producers to add warmth, depth, and subtle harmonic distortion to digital recordings.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_Phoenix.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_AC1\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_AC1 is a clone of a plugin, designed to emulate the characteristics and sonic qualities of analog mixing consoles. By simulating the behavior of analog circuits, the plugin brings the warmth, depth, and harmonic richness of analog gear to digital audio productions. The plugin is highly regarded for its ability to add subtle compression, harmonic distortion, and a sense of cohesion to mixes, making them sound more polished and professional.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_AC1.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_AC2\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_AC2 is a clone of a plugin designed to emulate the classic sound and behavior of analog tape machines that captures the essence of tape saturation, compression, and harmonic richness, making it an invaluable asset for adding depth, warmth, and character to digital recordings. The plugin provides a range of controls that allow users to fine-tune the tape emulation to suit various audio materials and production styles.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_AC2.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_RS124\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_RS124 is a clone of the first emulation of classic vari-mu compressor, originally developed in the 1960s by technical engineers of famous recording studio. This plugin captures the unique sonic characteristics and behavior of the original hardware, which was famously used on numerous iconic recordings by The Beatles and other legendary artists.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_RS124.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 \b \fs36 \u8220"JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter\u8221"\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter is a clone of freeware limiter plugin designed to provide transparent limiting, allowing you to maximize the loudness of your audio tracks without introducing distortion or unwanted artifacts. Simple interface, low CPU usage, and essential controls make it an excellent choice for both beginners and experienced producers looking to increase the loudness of their tracks. However, the developer of the plugin disappeared from the market abruptly around 2007.\par}
{\pard \ql \f0 \sa180 \li0 \fi0 {\field{\*\fldinst{HYPERLINK "https://github.com/JClones/JSFXClones/blob/master/JClones_Classic_Master_Limiter.md"}}{\fldrslt{\ul
Detailed Description
}}}
\par}
}
]]></description>
  </metadata>
</index>
